Finding Aid for University of Michigan. Buildings and Grounds Dept.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Glass Plate Negatives, 1918-1922 and undated
  - 46-University (Model) High School (Box 5)
  - 47-President's Home (Box 5)
- Topographical Maps, 1921-1938, (M4114 .A8:2U5 svar U5 Out)
  The series Topographical Maps (1921-1938) includes oversized maps which detail the topography of the area surrounding and including the University of Michigan.
  - Map of block bounded by Volland, Fourteenth, and Washington Streets, including Homeopathic Hospital and Storehouse. (M-1), Scale [1:240] 1"=20' (Folder 1)
  - Map of region in vicinity of Cat-Hole / surveyed by R.D. Granger; drawn by R.D. Granger. December 28, 1921 (M-3), Scale [1:480]. 1"=40' (Folder 1)
  - Stadia Survey of property bounded by East and South University, Washtenaw and Church December 30, 1921 (M-4), Scale [ca. 1:240] (Folder 1)
  - Survey of land bounded by the streets East and South University, Monroe and Haven / tr. K.D.C. December 23, 1921 (M-5), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20' (Folder 1)
  - Contour Map, property of the University of Michigan east of University Hospital / surveyed by Anderson, Bremenkampf, Heath, Roth (traced by) May 1925 (M-23), Scale [1:480]. 1"=40' (Folder 1)
  - Lots 1 to 9, 15 to 19, 11 except the north 60'-0" and the East 54'-0" of lot 10 block 4 of R.S. Smith's 3rd Addition, Ann Arbor, Michigan / survey by H.H. Atwell. June 1923 (M-52), Scale [1:192].1"=16'. (Folder 1)
  - Topographical survey, University High School plot / dr. by A.G.D. October 25, 1927 (M-55), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20' (Folder 1)
  - Topographical survey, block bound by Glen Dr., Observatory St., Washington Hgts.--Rev. map of 1921 / plane table survey by Surveying Dept., September 1928 (M-68), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20' (Folder 1)
  - Topographical map of proposed university garage site. February 10, 1930 (M-91), Scale [1:180]. 1"=15'. (Folder 1)
  - Topographical survey of psychopathic hospital site / by R.L.D.
    - May 10, 1930 (M-92), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20' (Folder 1)
    - January 29, 1931 (M-92), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20' (Folder 1)
  - Topographic survey of women's dormitory site along North University and Observatory St. / drawn by Jensen and Yee. October 15, 1938 (M-129), Scale [1:240]. 1"=240' (Folder 1)
  - Topographic survey of men's dormitory site along East University and Willard St. / drawn by Mort. October 1938 (M-130), Scale [1:240]. 1"=20'. (Folder 1)